Version 11.9.0
Usage: pnpm config set <key> <value>
       pnpm config get <key>
       pnpm config get --json <key>
       pnpm config delete <key>
       pnpm config list

Manage the pnpm configuration files.

Commands:
      delete               Remove the config key from the config file
      get                  Print the config value for the provided key
      list                 Show all the config settings
      set                  Set the config key to the value provided

Options:
  -g, --global                     Sets the configuration in the global config
                                   file
      --json                       Show all types of values in JSON format (not
                                   just objects and arrays)
      --location <project|global>  When set to "project", the
                                   pnpm-workspace.yaml file will be used if it
                                   exists. If only .npmrc exists, it will be
                                   used. If neither exists, a
                                   pnpm-workspace.yaml file will be created.

Visit https://pnpm.io/11.x/cli/config for documentation about this command.
